Finding Aid for Stephen M. Ross School of Business (University of Michigan) records, 1916-2017
Bentley Historical Library
- Floyd A. Bond and Successors Series, 1926-1984; 1960-1979
  - Dean's Administrative, 1926-1983; 1960-1979
    - Affirmative Action
      - General
        - 1972-1973 (Box 41)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 41)
      - Handicapped, 1977-1978 (Box 41)
      - Instructional Salaries, 1978 (Box 41)
      - LEAD Program, 1980-1983 (Box 41)
      - Minority Student Survey, 1973-1977 (Box 41)
      - Ph.D in Business Administration, 1975-1977 (Box 41)
      - Placement Activity Record, 1972 (Box 41)
      - Regents (meeting with), May 1973 (Box 41)
      - Reports (Box 42)
        - 1970-1971 (Box 42)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 42)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 42)
        - 1973-1975 (Box 42)
        - 1976 (Box 42)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 42)
        - 1978 (Box 42)
      - Search for Minorities and Women, 1972-1973 (Box 42)
      - Title IX Self-Examination (Women), 1976-1978 (Box 42)
      - Tuskegee Institute, 1976-1978 (Box 42)
      - Women, 1971-1972 (Box 42)
      - Workshop, November, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Aluminum Company of America (ALCOA), 1969 (Box 42)
    - Alpha Kappa Psi Foundation, 1968 (Box 42)
    - Alumni
      - Black Business Students Alumni Day, 1977-1978 (Box 42)
      - Building a Data Base, 1979 (Box 42)
      - Class Agents, 1975-1979 (Box 42)
      - Class Reunions, 1973-1983 (Box 42)
      - Conferences, 1929-1968 (Box 42)
      - Evaluation of Class Officers Questionnaire, 1969 (Box 42)
      - Director of Alumni Relations
        - 1971-1976 (Box 42)
        - 1979-1983 (Box 42)
      - General
        - 1961-1969 (Box 42)
        - 1970-1979 (Box 42)
      - International Organizing, 1976 (Box 42)
    - American Can Company, 1964 (Box 42)
    - Annual Reports (generally background information)
      - 1961-1962 (Box 42)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 42)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 42)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 42)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 42)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 42)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 42)
      - 1970-1971 (Box 42)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 43)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 43)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 43)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 43)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 43)
    - Arthur Anderson and Co., 1967-1975 (Box 43)
    - B General, 1963-1964; 1976 (Box 43)
    - Bond, Floyd
      - Correspondence and Memos
        - Chronological
          - 1960-1961 (Box 43)
          - 1962 (Box 43)
          - 1963, 2 folders (Box 43)
          - 1964, 2 folders (Box 43)
          - 1965, 3 folders (Box 43)
          - 1966, 2 folders (Box 43)
          - 1966, 3 folders (Box 44)
          - 1967, 4 folders (Box 44)
          - 1968, 3 folders (Box 44)
          - 1969 (Box 44)
          - 1970 (Box 44)
          - 1970-1971 (Box 44)
          - 1971-1972 (Box 44)
          - 1972 (Box 45)
          - 1972-1973 (Box 45)
          - 1973-1974, 2 folders (Box 45)
          - 1974-1975, 3 folders (Box 45)
          - 1975 (Box 45)
          - 1975-1976, 4 folders (Box 45)
          - 1976 (Box 45)
          - 1976 (Box 46)
          - 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box 46)
          - 1977 (Box 46)
          - 1977-1978, 3 folders (Box 46)
          - 1978-1979 (Box 46)
        - Topical
          - Deanships Available, 1963-1972 (Box 46)
          - Faculty, 1965-1970 (Box 46)
          - Intra-University, 1963-1971 (Box 46)
          - Positions Open, 1963-1972 (Box 46)
    - Bowman, D.O., 1970-1973 (Box 46)
    - Budget
      - Account Numbers, 1968-1976 (Box 46)
      - Annual
        - 1960/61 (Box 47)
        - 1961/62
          - Hospital Administration (Box 47)
          - Preliminary (Box 47)
          - Staff Requests (Box 47)
        - 1962/63
          - General (Box 47)
          - Preliminary (Box 47)
        - 1963/64
          - General (Box 47)
          - Preliminary (Box 47)
        - 1964/65
          - General (Box 47)
          - Preliminary (Box 47)
        - 1965/66
          - General (Box 47)
          - Preliminary, 2 folders (Box 47)
        - 1966/67
          - General (Box 47)
          - Preliminary (Box 47)
        - 1967/68
          - General (Box 47)
          - Preliminary (Box 47)
        - 1968/69
          - General (Box 47)
          - Preliminary (Box 47)
        - 1969/70
          - General (Box 47)
          - Preliminary (Box 47)
        - 1971/72
          - Bureau of Business Research (Box 47)
          - Cuts (Box 47)
          - Departmental Equipment (Box 47)
          - International Commerce (Box 47)
          - Library (Box 47)
          - Management Education (Box 47)
          - MBA Evening Program (Box 47)
          - Preliminary (Box 47)
          - Projections through, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
          - School (Box 47)
        - 1972/73
          - Conferences (Box 47)
          - General, 2 folders (Box 47)
          - International Commerce (Box 47)
          - Library (Box 47)
          - Management Education (Box 47)
          - MBA Evening Program (Box 47)
          - Projections (Box 47)
        - 1973/74
          - Administrative Cost Allocation through, 1976-1977 (Box 47)
          - Conference (and Budget Projections through ), 1978-1979 (Box 47)
          - Division of Management Education (Box 47)
          - Division of Research (Box 48)
          - General (Box 48)
          - International Commerce (Box 48)
          - Library (Box 48)
          - MBA Evening Program (Box 48)
          - Request (and 5 year projections) (Box 48)
          - School (Box 48)
        - 1975/76
          - Conference (Box 48)
          - Division of Management Education (Box 48)
          - Division of Research (Box 48)
          - General (Box 48)
          - Instructors and Other Teaching Staff (Box 48)
          - International Commerce (Box 48)
          - Library (Box 48)
          - MBA Evening Program (Box 48)
          - Request (Box 48)
          - Scholarships (Box 48)
          - School (Box 48)
          - Travel (Box 48)
        - 1976/77
          - Breakdown of Budget (Box 48)
          - Conference (Box 48)
          - Division of Management Education (Box 48)
          - Division of Research (Box 48)
          - General (Box 48)
          - International Commerce (Box 48)
          - Library (Box 48)
          - MBA Evening Program (Box 48)
          - Priorities Committee (Box 48)
          - Requests (Box 48)
          - Scholarships (Box 48)
          - School (Box 48)
        - 1977/78
          - Conference, 2 folders (Box 48)
          - Division of Management Education (Box 48)
          - Division of Research (Box 48)
          - General (Box 48)
          - International Commerce (Box 48)
          - Library (Box 48)
          - MBA Evening Program (Box 48)
          - Scholarships (Box 48)
          - School (Box 48)
        - 1978/79
          - Conference (Box 48)
          - Division of Management Education (Box 48)
          - Division of Research (Box 48)
          - Instructional Staff Salary Analysis (Box 48)
          - International Commerce (Box 48)
          - Library (Box 48)
          - MBA Evening Program (Box 48)
          - Request (Box 49)
          - Scholarships (Box 49)
          - School (Box 49)
          - Special Salary Survey (Box 49)
        - 1979/80
          - Conference (Box 49)
          - Scholarships (Box 49)
      - Extension Teaching Stipends, 1959-1963 (Box 49)
      - Faculty Salary Cost/Credit Hour, 1971 (Box 49)
      - Instructional Staff Salary Analysis, 1975-1976 (Box 49)
      - Merit Increases, 1971-1978 (Box 49)
      - Organization Report, 1978 (Box 49)
      - Performance Budget Evaluation System, 1971-1974 (Box 49)
      - State Auditors, 1967-1968 (Box 49)
      - Statistical Data, 1976 (Box 49)
    - Business Hall of Fame
      - Advisory Board, 1961-1969 (Box 49)
      - Electors, 1968-1975 (Box 49)
      - General, 1966-1970 (Box 49)
    - Business School, National Survey Ratings, 1972-1976 (Box 49)
    - C General, 1961-1962 (Box 49)
    - California, University of, 1962 (Box 49)
    - Carnegie Corporation, 1964-1965 (Box 49)
    - Center for Research Utilization, 1963 (Box 49)
    - College Resources Analysis System (CRA)
      - 1970, 2 folders (Box 49)
      - 1971
        - Fall (Box 49)
        - Winter (Box 49)
        - Tables (Box 49)
        - Teaching Loads (Box 49)
      - 1973 (Box 49)
      - 1974 (Box 49)
      - 1975
        - Fall (Box 49)
        - Winter (Box 49)
      - 1976 (Box 49)
    - Columbia University Study, 1974 (Box 49)
    - Commencement and Honors Convocation
      - 1964-1965 (Box 50)
      - 1965, 2 folders (Box 50)
      - 1966, 2 folders (Box 50)
      - 1967, 2 folders (Box 50)
      - 1968, 3 folders (Box 50)
      - 1969, 2 folders (Box 50)
      - 1970, 4 folders (Box 50)
      - 1971, 4 folders (Box 50)
      - 1972, 4 folders (Box 50)
      - 1973, 4 folders (Box 50)
      - 1974, 3 folders (Box 50)
      - 1975, 3 folders (Box 50)
      - 1976, 5 folders (Box 50)
      - 1977, 4 folders (Box 50)
      - 1978, 4 folders (Box 50)
      - 1979, 2 folders (Box 50)
      - Miscellaneous, 1961-1977 (Box 50)
    - Community Colleges, 1970-1972 (Box 50)
    - CPA Congratulatory Letters, 1966-1967 (Box 50)
    - Cyphernetics, 1976 (Box 50)
    - D General, 1962-1968 (Box 50)
    - Data-base Systems Research Group, 1977 (Box 50)
    - Dean's Conference
      - 1960-1961 (Box 50)
      - 1961-1962 (Box 50)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 50)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 50)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 50)
    - Dean's Forum
      - 1967, 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Dean's State of the School Address
      - 1971 (Box 50)
      - 1973 (Box 50)
      - 1974 (Box 50)
      - 1977, 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Dearborn Center [see also "Supplemental Records", "Programs for Full-Time Students and Faculty", Masters of Business Administration]
      - Executive Committee
        - 1959-1960 (Box 50)
        - 1961 (Box 50)
        - 1962-1964 (Box 50)
      - Fairlane Forum, 1961 (Box 50)
      - History (Box 50)
      - Plan, 1957 (Box 50)
    - Degrees Granted (Summary), 1926-1970 (Box 50)
    - Detroit Free Press, 1962 (Box 50)
    - Dow Chemical Company, 1969 (Box 50)
    - E General, 1961-1972 (Box 50)
    - Economic Education Resources Proposal, 1966-1967 (Box 50)
    - Enrollment
      - Out-of-State, 1961-1962 (Box 50)
      - Ph.D, 1971-1973 (Box 50)
      - Projections
        - 1963-1964 (Box 50)
        - 1963-1971 (Box 50)
        - 1974-1978 (Box 51)
      - Staff Needs, 1965-1967 (Box 51)
      - Statistics, 1924-1978; 1 folder, 2 volumes (Box 51)
      - Student Fees, 1973-1979 (Box 51)
      - Study, 1960 (Box 51)
    - European Foundation for Management Development, 1972 (Box 51)
    - Evaluation
      - Conference, 1976 (Box 51)
      - Phase I (Box 51)
      - Phase II (Box 51)
    - F General, 1961-1967 (Box 51)
    - Facilities
      - Adams, Thomas T., 1965-1968 (Box 51)
      - Advanced Management Center Proposal, 1975-1976 (Box 51)
      - Assembly Hall, 1963-1973; 7 folders, 3 volumes (Box 51)
      - Early Building Needs Assessments, 1928-1945 (Box 52)
      - Elevators, 1963-1976 (Box 52)
      - Equipment, 1973-1975 (Box 52)
      - Kalmbach Management Center, 1972-1977 (Box 52)
      - Paton Accounting Center, 1965-1979; 26 folders, 2 volumes (Box 52)
      - Planning, 1965 (Box 53)
      - Office Space, 1960-1969 (Box 53)
      - Regents Communications, 1973-1976 (Box 53)
      - Room Utilization, 1963-1972 (Box 53)
      - Site Plan, 1980 (Box 53)
      - Space Requirements, 1965 (Box 53)
    - Finance Club, 1967 (Box 53)
    - Financial Aid
      - 1960-1975, 3 folders (Box 53)
      - 1971-1975, 4 folders (Box 53)
    - Ford Foundation
      - European Doctoral Fellowships, 1971-1972; 3 folders (Box 53)
      - General, 1963-1971 (Box 53)
      - Intensive Summer Program on Application of Behavioral Sciences to Business Administration, 1962 (Box 53)
    - Ford, Henry II, 1968 (Box 53)
    - Ford Motor Company, 1962-1966 (Box 53)
    - Form Letters
      - 1962 (Box 53)
      - 1964 (Box 53)
    - Fundraising
      - Annual Giving, 1974-1979 (Box 53)
      - Bond, Floyd, personal contributing (Box 53)
      - Capital Fund Campaign, 1979-1980 (Box 53)
      - $55 Million Campaign, 1965-1967 (Box 53)
      - General, 1961-1978 (Box 53)
      - Lewis, David, 1970 (Box 53)
      - Paton Fund, 1963-1970 (Box 53)
      - Solicitation Letters, 1964-1977 (Box 53)
      - Summary of Gifts and Donors, 1969-1978 (Box 53)
    - G General, 1963-1964 (Box 53)
    - General Electric Company, 1963-1965 (Box 53)
    - General Mills, Inc., 1967 (Box 53)
    - General Motors, 1961-1975 (Box 53)
    - Georgia, University of, 1973 (Box 53)
    - Grade Distribution (undergraduate), 1963-1979 (Box 54)
    - Griffith, William Jr., 1974 (Box 54)
    - H General, 1962 (Box 54)
    - Hale, Clayton G., 1969-1974 (Box 54)
    - Harvard University
      - Executive Program Study, 1958-1966 (Box 54)
      - General, 1960-1966 (Box 54)
    - Herzog, Bertram, 1965 (Box 54)
    - History
      - Christian Science Monitor Articles, 1957-1961; 2 folders (Box 54)
      - Clippings, 1964-1978 (Box 54)
      - Encyclopedic History Drafts, 1976 (Box 54)
      - Fiftieth Anniversary, 1974-1975 (Box 54)
      - General, 1926-1982 (Box 54)
      - Name, 1963 (Box 54)
    - Honors [see Commencement and Honors] (Box 54)
    - Hopson, Jean B., 1975-1976 (Box 54)
    - Indiana University, 1961-1963 (Box 54)
    - Institute for Social Research, 1973 (Box 54)
    - Instructional Computing, University-wide Review, 1977-1978 (Box 54)
    - International Survey of Management Education, 1968-1969 (Box 54)
    - K General, 1961-1971 (Box 54)
    - Kalamazoo Study, 1966-1967 (Box 54)
    - L General, 1964 (Box 54)
    - Library, Business Administration, 1960-1978 (Box 54)
    - Lincoln National Life, 1962-1963 (Box 54)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of, Proposal, 1968 (Box 54)
    - Mc General, 1962 (Box 54)
    - McGraw-Hill Proposal, 1969 (Box 54)
    - M General, 1962-1963 (Box 54)
    - Marketing Club, 1967-1972 (Box 54)
    - Medallions, 1976-1977 (Box 54)
    - Michigan Council of Business School Deans, 1970-1974 (Box 54)
    - Michigan Council on Economic Education, 1965 (Box 54)
    - Michigan Scholars in College Teaching Program, 1963-1973 (Box 54)
    - Michigan, State of, 1961-1974 (Box 54)
    - Michigan State University
      - General, 1962-1966 (Box 54)
      - Proposed Utility Institute, 1964 (Box 54)
    - Muller, William G., 1972-1973 (Box 55)
    - Moratorium, 1969 (Box 55)
    - National Merit Scholarships, 1963-1964 (Box 55)
    - National Science Foundation, 1962 (Box 55)
    - Newsweek, 1967 (Box 55)
    - O General, 1960-1969 (Box 55)
    - Operating Trends of School, 1964-1967 (Box 55)
    - P General, 1960-1973 (Box 55)
    - Pass-Fail Option, 1970 (Box 55)
    - Peer Study, 1972-1977 (Box 55)
    - Phi Kappa Phi, 1962-1970 (Box 55)
    - Placement/Employment
      - Career Planning Study, 1977 (Box 55)
      - General, 1964-1978; 2 folders (Box 55)
      - Placement Office, 1960-1981; 3 folders (Box 55)
    - Policy Compilations, 1974 (Box 55)
    - Pomona College [see also Personal sub-series], 1961-1967 (Box 55)
    - Power, Eugene, 1965-1971 (Box 55)
    - Price-Waterhouse Proposal, 1978-1979 (Box 55)
    - Princeton Conference of Deans, 1961 (Box 55)
    - Product Development and Management Association, 1977 (Box 55)
    - Program Evaluation Reports, 1974-1976; 2 folders (Box 55)
    - Public Relations (David Lewis), 1964-1974 (Box 55)
    - Publications (Materials related to...)
      - Alumni Bulletin, 1965-1969 (Box 55)
      - Alumni Newsletter, 1962-1969 (Box 55)
      - Bulletin, 1962-1974 (Box 55)
      - Cisler, Walker, Autobiography, 1972-1975 (Box 55)
      - Dividend, 1968-1977; 2 folders (Box 55)
      - Michigan Business Review, 1959-1974 (Box 55)
      - Monroe Street Journal, 1960-1982 (Box 56)
      - Ruthven, Alexander G., biography, 1974-1975 (Box 56)
      - Series of Entrepreneurial Autobiographies, 1966 (Box 56)
    - Questionnaire on the Graduate School, 1962 (Box 113)
    - R General, 1961-1976 (Box 56)
    - Recruiting Policy (University), 1971 (Box 56)
    - Recruitment Reports, 1962-1973; 4 folders (Box 56)
    - Roberts, Robert (Memos)
      - 1968-1970, 10 folders (Box 56)
    - S General, 1961-1963 (Box 57)
    - St. Lawrence Seaway World Conference Proposal, 1968 (Box 57)
    - Sebastian S. Kresge Professorship, 1966-1969; 1977-1978 (Box 57)
    - Shri Ram Center, 1963-1964 (Box 57)
    - Special Lecturers, 1959-1970
      - [card files 1 and 2 in box 94] (Box 57)
    - Staff Opinion Survey Questionnaire, 1976 (Box 57)
    - Stanford University, 1963 (Box 57)
    - State Technical Services Act, 1965 (Box 57)
    - Stilec, C.E., 1970 (Box 57)
    - Student Council, 1963-1965 (Box 113)
    - Students
      - Appeal Procedures, 1974-1976 (Box 57)
      - Belmont Scholarship Fund, 1967-1968 (Box 57)
      - Governance, 1975 (Box 57)
      - Grade Distribution, 1977 (Box 57)
      - Graduate Students
        - Affirmative Action Program, 1975-1977 (Box 57)
        - Assistantship Program, 1973-1975 (Box 57)
        - Associateship Program, 1971-1972 (Box 57)
        - Availability Pool Data, 1974-1977 (Box 57)
        - General, 1972-1975 (Box 57)
      - Organizations, 1959-1980; 2 folders (Box 57)
      - Ph.D Students
        - Qualifying Examinations, 1948-1972; 2 folders (Box 57)
      - Records, 1973-1978 (Box 57)
      - Scholarships [card files 3 and 4 in box 94], 1962-1971 (Box 57)
      - Student Council, 1960-1972; 5 folders (Box 57)
      - Student Council, 1972-1979; 7 folders (Box 58)
      - Survey of Admitted M.P. Students, 1969-1970; 1974 (Box 58)
      - Survey of Undergraduates, 1959-1969 (Box 58)
      - Title IX (Gender Discrimination) Grievance, 1976 (Box 58)
      - Transfer, 1940-1960 (Box 58)
      - Unauthorized Surveys by Students, 1968 (Box 58)
      - Unrest/Protest, 1965-1972 (Box 58)
    - Swinyard, Al, 1978 (Box 58)
    - T General, 1961-1962 (Box 58)
    - Thornton, Charles B., 1967-1968 (Box 58)
    - U General, 1962 (Box 58)
    - United States Government, 1964-1965 (Box 58)
    - University Deans Club, 1979 (Box 58)
    - W General, 1961-1962 (Box 58)
    - Washington Campus Program, Inc., 1978 (Box 58)
    - Wayne State University-University of Michigan Dual Elections, 1961 (Box 58)
    - Weaver, Richard L., 1965 (Box 58)
    - Whitaker, Gilbert R
      - Appointment as Dean, 1978-1979 (Box 58)
      - Correspondence and Memos, 1979-1983 (Box 58)
    - Women, 1968-1974 (Box 58)
  - Supplemental Administrative Records, 1951-1983
    The school's Supplemental Administrative Records, are similar to those found in the Stevenson series, but in the Bond series they are arranged in a more complex manner, reflecting the school's growing administrative sophistication. There are four subseries: Committees, Faculty and Administrative Staff, Programs for Full-Time Faculty and Administrative Staff and Programs for Special Groups.
    - Committees, 1951-1981; 1961-1978
      Committees, 1951-81 (primarily 1961-78), is an alphabetical file of records mostly created by the school's many faculty committees. Most interesting are the Academic and Admissions, Curriculum, Doctoral Studies, Executive, and Visiting Committees. For reasons of confidentiality records of the Academic and Admissions committee, which passed upon all applications for admission, as well as on the fate of students who failed to maintain an acceptable grade point average, have been modified by the Bentley Library to mask the names of individual students. Despite this modification, it is usually possible to determine both the gender and race of applicants and students.
      - Academic and Admissions
        - 1961-1965 (Box 58)
        - 1964-1967 (Box 58)
        - 1968-1971 (Box 58)
        - 1972-1974 (Box 58)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 58)
      - Accounting Advisory Board (Paton Accounting Center), 1975-1978 (Box 58)
      - Actuarial Advisory Board, 1961-1969 (Box 58)
      - Adult Education, 1961-1972 (Box 58)
      - Alumni Advisory, 1964-1969 (Box 58)
      - Alumni Relations, 1961-1966 (Box 58)
      - Awards
        - Awards and Honors, 1961-1964 (Box 59)
        - Honorary Degree Nominations
          - 1961-1969 (Box 59)
          - 1970-1975 (Box 59)
        - University Awards, Nominations
          - 1963-1969 (Box 59)
          - 1970-1976 (Box 59)
          - 1977-1978 (Box 59)
      - Bachelor of Business Administration Degree Study
        - 1968-1970 (Box 59)
      - Building, 1964-1968 (Box 59)
      - Computer Use
        - 1964-1969 (Box 59)
        - 1970-1975 (Box 59)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 59)
      - Curriculum
        - BBA Core Course Coordinating Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 59)
        - Curriculum Committee
          - 1960-1961 (Box 59)
          - 1961-1962
            - General (Box 59)
            - Report re. Statistics 490 (Box 59)
          - 1962-1963 (Box 59)
          - 1963-1964 (Box 60)
            - General (Box 60)
            - Honors Program (Box 60)
          - 1964-1965 (Box 60)
          - 1965-1966 (Box 60)
          - 1966-1967, 2 folders (Box 60)
          - 1967-1968, 2 folders (Box 60)
          - 1968-1969 (Box 60)
          - 1969-1970 (Box 60)
          - 1970-1971 (Box 60)
          - 1971-1972 (Box 60)
          - 1972-1973 (Box 60)
          - 1973-1974 (Box 60)
        - MBA Core Course Coordinating Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 60)
        - MBA Degree Study Committee
          - 1966 (Box 60)
          - 1966-1967 (Box 60)
      - Deanship
        - 1959-1960 (Box 61)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 61)
      - Doctoral Studies
        - 1960-1963 (Box 61)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 61)
        - 1966, 2 folders (Box 61)
        - 1967 (Box 61)
        - 1968-1969 (Box 61)
        - 1970-1971 (Box 61)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 61)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 61)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 61)
      - Drafting Committee, 1969 (Box 61)
      - Employment, Ad Hoc Committee on Outside, 1966-1979 (Box 61)
      - Enrollment, 1960-1961 (Box 61)
      - Excellence, 1968-1972 (Box 61)
      - Executive
        - 1960-1967 (Box 61)
        - 1967-1969 (Box 61)
        - 1969-1970 (Box 61)
        - 1970-1971 (Box 62)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 62)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 62)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 62)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 62)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 62)
      - Extension Service, 1959-1964 (Box 62)
      - Facility Planning, 1979-1981 (Box 62)
      - Grading, 1973-1974 (Box 62)
      - Graduate and/or Undergraduate Status
        - 1960-1961 (Box 62)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 62)
      - Internal Departmentalization, 1962 (Box 62)
      - International Business, 1977 (Box 62)
      - International Programs (Ford Foundation)
        - General
          - 1960 (Box 62)
          - 1961 (Box 62)
          - 1961-1963 (Box 62)
          - 1965-1967 (Box 62)
          - 1968-1971 (Box 62)
      - Judiciary
        - 1967-1969 (Box 63)
        - 1970-1973 (Box 63)
      - Library, 1961-1978 (Box 63)
      - Management Education, 1971 (Box 63)
      - Operations and Planning (includes departmental organizational committees)
        - 1962-1965 (Box 63)
        - 1966-1969 (Box 63)
        - 1970-1978 (Box 63)
      - Placement, 1970-1973 (Box 63)
      - Promotions, 1961-1962 (Box 63)
      - Regional Science, 1960-1961 (Box 63)
      - Social, 1960-1977 (Box 63)
      - Special Committee Reports, 1961-1969 (Box 64)
      - Standing Committees Membership, 1951-1979; 2 folders (Box 64)
      - Students' Role in Decision Making, 1967-1971 (Box 64)
      - Teaching, 1964-1979 (Box 64)
      - UAW Office-Clerical Contract, 1975 (Box 64)
      - Visiting Committee
        - 1969-1971 (Box 64)
        - 1972 (Box 64)
        - 1973 (Box 64)
        - 1975 (Box 64)
        - 1978 (Box 64)
    - Faculty and Administrative Staff